Previously on:
Billy called.
Billy Stanhope?
Yeah, he said he has
a business proposition for you.
How 'bout that?
Billy Stanhope...
(laughs)
(screaming)
(screams)
What went down between you two?
Well, we built Eddie's software
company in Bridget's garage
and then sold it
for a couple billion dollars.
That son of a bitch.
He didn't want to sell.
You really think we can finally
build the electric suitcase?
Yes, we have the technology now.
I-I just need you to help me
write the code.
Hey, you know, while
we're on the subject...
What? Peeing?
No, sex.
There's something
you should know.
It's about your ex-wife.
What? Bridget?
Yeah, I'm, uh...
kind of sleeping with her.
What?!
W-Wait, hey...
Mom, this is Alan.
Alan, this is
my mom, Jean.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
You know what?
Tell you what.
I will call my mom
and try to set up a dinner.
Evelyn says there's a place
right down the street
where they have
music and dancing.
Why don't you two
fuddy-duddies run along
and let Jean and I
have some fun.
You think we'll find some
cute fellas to dance with?
Oh, Jean, Jean, Jean...
we're not going to dance.
I adore your mother.
That's only because
you just met her.
I don't know.
I think I got
to know her pretty well.
Good morning, darling.
Hi, Peaches.
♪ Men...♪
Great. I'll pick you up
at the airport.
I can't wait.
I love you, too.
Tell Zoey I said "hi."
Oh, Alan says "hi."
(quietly)
Yes, he's still here.
Uh-huh. I know. You're right.
She says "hi" back.
Okay, I'll see
you tomorrow.
Here you go.
Oh, thank you.
You got to be excited about
having your girlfriend back.
What has it been, a month?
Three weeks.
Still, that's like
a decade in penis years.
Yeah.
Tell you the truth, I'm actually
a little bit worried.
About your relationship?
Come on. Absence makes the heart
grow fonder.
At least for guys like you.
For guys like me,
absence is more often enforced
by the state of California.
Zoey doesn't know that I started
a new software company
with my old partner.
Yeah, with Billy, I know.
What's the big deal?
Well, there's
a third partner...
that Zoey's
not gonna like.
Walden...
you made me a partner?
All I did was bring
you two guys together,
The third partner is Bridget.
Your ex-wife?
Come on, I brought
you two guys together!
But she helped me design
the original code
for the software;
I had to bring her in.
Oh, right, right.
Well, I guess that would make
a very awkward conversation
with Zoey.
Yeah. I think I'm just gonna try
to slip it in
without her noticing.
Hmm. Story of my life.
(sighs)
Well, listen, just remember,
that love will get you
through times of no money
better than money will get you
through times of no love.
That's good advice.
Thank you.
And, uh, just to be clear...
uh, I have zero stake
in this potential
billion-dollar business?
Well, actually, I
was gonna give you
a hundred shares
of founders' stock.
Wow.
If this thing works,
it could be worth millions.
Thank you.
My problem is I still
got to figure out
how to explain this to Zoey.
Dump the bitch. Don't let her
screw this up for us.
Once again, thank you
for the advice.
Well, if it makes you
feel any better,
I've got my own little
relationship problem brewing.
Yeah, that doesn't
make me feel better.
My girlfriend's mom and my mom
have become lovers.
(laughs): Okay, that does
make me feel better.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Men, men, men, manly men ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ohh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Men, men, men, manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ah. ♪
♪ Men. ♪
♪ Two and a Half Men 9x20 ♪
Grandma's Pie
Original Air Date on April 9, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪ Men... ♪
Can I ask you a question?
What?
If we just had sex in England,
would I be lying on
the other side of the bed?
(laughs)
Oh, God, I've missed you.
I missed you, too.
And you can call me Walden.
(laughing)
So, what have
you been up to?
Actually, I've been,
like, very, very busy.
With what?
I started a new
software company
with my old partner
Billy Stanhope.
(gasps)
Walden!
Yeah.
That's terrific!
It's amazing and, and
we built this
amazing product.
It's called
the electric suitcase.
I-It's gonna completely
revolutionize
the global energy market.
Whoa. Sounds big.
No, it's bigger than big.
I mean, the three of us
could end up splitting
billions of dollars.
The three of you?
What?
You just said
the three of you.
Y-Yes, there are
in fact three of us.
Who's the third?
Oh, not Alan.
(laughs)
No, God, no.
So, who is it?
It's Bridget.
Your ex-wife?
There's nothing I could do.
I mean, she helped write the
original code for the software
so she still owns
a third of it.
So you've gone into
business with a woman
who drove her car
into your living room
because you chose me
over her?
Crazy world, huh?
On the plus side...
s-she's sleeping with
my ex-partner. So...
Why is that a plus side?
B-Because she's with him,
so you don't have to worry
about me and... her.
I wasn't worried
about you and her.
Good.
Until just now.
Why didn't you tell me
about this before we had sex?
Do you want to have sex now?
No!
That's why!
I'm going home.
Oh, come on, Zoey.
Don't make a big deal
out of this.
If I told you I was going into
business with my ex-husband
would you consider it
a big deal?
No, not at all.
You're a liar.
(groans)
Life would be so much easier
if I dated dumb chicks.
I heard that.
It was a compliment.
Here you go.
Thank you. So..
have you given any thought
as to what we're gonna do
about our little...
mother situation?
Golden Girls Gone Wild?
Hey... what can we do?
They're grown woman.
They've made
a lifestyle choice.
I have no problem
with the lifestyle.
I've tried the lifestyle.
Really?! When?
Who? College? Camp?
Shut up, Alan.
Sorry. Go ahead.
How am I supposed to have
a relationship with you
when your mother is clearly
taking sexual advantage of mine?
H-Hang on a second.
I don't think anyone is
taking advantage of anyone.
You don't?
A week ago my mother was living
in a retirement community
playing golf
with her girlfriends
and watching reruns
of Cagney & Lacey.
Well, I don't know.
Golf, Cagney & Lacey...
Sounds like she was
already halfway there.
Shut up, Alan.
(both laughing)
Oh, good, you're here.
Mom!
What have you done
to yourself?
Evelyn took me shopping.
Do you like my new look?
Isn't she gorgeous?
Yeah, I-I guess.
We also got matching tattoos.
Oh, Mom, no.
See? It's
a little heart.
Uh, with an
"E plus J" in it.
I don't see one
on your ankle, Mom.
It's not on my ankle.
Oh, glory-oski.
Mom, you've been gone all day.
I thought you and I were gonna
spend some time together
before you went back
to Sunset Village.
I know.
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
We've been so busy.
But don't worry.
You're gonna be seeing
a lot more of me
after I move in with Evy.
What?
I've got this huge place.
Why shouldn't she enjoy it?
You're talking about
your huge house, right?
We're just gonna pick up
some things here
and then go close up
Jean's condo.
And then we'll start
our new life,
right, Peaches?
That's right, Pumpkin.
Come on.
This sort of makes you
brother and sister, doesn't it?
Is it just me or is...
that idea kind of a turn-on?
(laughs):
It's just me.
♪ Men...♪
WALDEN: Oh, come on.
It's not that weird.
Yeah, because we have
a child together.
Okay, well, Bridget and I
have a business together.
It's basically the same thing.
Have you been sniffing glue?
No! They both require
nurturing and attention.
The only difference is your
kid's gonna cost you a fortune
and mine is gonna
make a fortune.
Wow. Good-bye.
Okay, wait, wait,
wait, wait.
J-Just...
do one thing for me.
What?
Let's the three of us
have dinner together.
You want me to have dinner
with you and your ex-wife?
Yes.
That way you can see that
everything is cool between us.
Come on, Zoey.
This is really important to me.
(sighs)
God, I'm gonna regret this.
One dinner.
Thank you.
I will see you tomorrow.
Good-bye.
(groans):
Well done, old boy.
You dodged the crazy
girlfriend bullet.
ZOEY: Walden, I'm still
outside the door.
You didn't let me finish.
All right, finish.
I love you so much.
♪ Men...♪
Here you go.
Thank you.
So did you tell Zoey
about working with Bridget?
Uh, yeah.
How'd it go?
Not good.
But she did agree
to have dinner with us.
W-Wait, you're having dinner
with your girlfriend
and your ex-wife?
Bad idea?
Well, not as bad as me trying
to turn my girlfriend on
with a little incest fantasy,
but it's right up there.
What else was I gonna do?
Well, I...
I'm not gonna dump the bitch.
Okay.
Fine, fine. We'll just keep
our eyes on the prize here.
What, your hundred shares
in the company?
I was more thinking
about your happiness,
but sure, there's that.
Hey, uh, this might
make you feel better.
Uh, I'm having my own
bad idea dinner.
What's that?
Lyndsey, her son, my son,
and the two gay grandmas.
Once again,
that does make me feel better.
(laughs)
Hey, how about this?
Why don't we meet back here
after our respective dinners
and compare notes?
Sort of like a recap at the end
of a reality show.
Yeah. Yeah, we could, uh,
you know, have a little contest.
See whose dinner was worse.
Shame we can't let
America vote on it.
(laughs)
Yeah.
Or can we?
♪ Men. ♪
Hey, this is really nice, huh?
Zoey, uh...
(clears throat)
Bridget and I
were talking about your...
...your concerns, and
Bridget was very eager
to assuage them.
Right, Bridge?
Absolutely.
Okay.
Let the assuaging begin.
Anybody?
I'll take a
crack at it.
No, thank you, Berta.
All right, obviously,
this is an awkward situation.
Walden and I were
together for many, many years,
and you and he have been dating
for a few months now,
so clearly, you're insecure
about us working together.
I am not insecure.
Right, and there's no reason
you should be. Yes,
I've known this guy
since high school,
and yes, we fell in love,
and yes, we spent
many happy years together,
but the reality now is,
we're simply business partners.
Right.
And not all those years
were happy.
Oh, sure, there were
some great times.
Also, I want to build...
But there were also
some bad times.
Also some bad times.
I mean, the point is,
is that our relationship now
is just strictly business.
Oh, speaking of which, we need
to upgrade the ventilation
for the server farm.
Oh, that's a good idea.
Oh, also, I want to build
triple redundancy.
Of course, but we shouldn't be
talking shop
and leaving poor Zoey
out of the conversation.
No, that's all right. I love
to hear about Walden's work.
Oh, that's so sweet.
I'm so glad
he found someone like you.
Oh. Thank you.
After I threw him out,
I wondered how he'd survive.
He's so needy.
I'm not needy.
Yeah, you are.
BOTH: Yes, you are.
So what's the deal?
Are you guys in it
for the long haul,
or are you just gonna date
and see what happens?
Well, we're just finding
our way for the moment.
(clears throat)
Oh, good.
Mm.
Good.
Keep it casual.
That way no one can accuse you
of going after his money.
Excuse me?
I'm not after his money.
Oh, no, you misunderstand.
I... I'm sure you're not,
but unfortunately,
there's no way to prove it.
Luckily, I met him
when he had nothing,
so there's no question
about my intentions.
Are you questioning
my intentions?
No, she's not. She's not.
No, you're not.
You're not, are you?
Of course not.
Are you questioning
my intentions?
Me? No!
Berta, how is
the pot roast coming?
Got another 30 minutes.
You guys keep chatting.
♪ Men. ♪
I don't understand.
Why is my grandmother
living with his grandmother?
Yeah, I was kind of
wondering that myself,
but I didn't want
to look stupid.
Too late, dude.
You want to handle this, Alan?
Not really.
I wasn't asking.
All right. Um...
Well, fellas, um,
your two grandmas are,
uh... are both very lonely,
and so, they've, uh, decided
to become...
uh, roommates, uh,
and keep each other company.
Oh, that makes sense.
Mm.
Plus, if one of them
falls down,
the other can call
the ambulance.
What if they both fall down
at the same time?
Um, I guess they starve
to death and die.
Unless they go cannibal
and try to eat each other.
If that happens,
I'm betting
on my grandma
eating your grandma.
Dude, there's no way
in the world
that your grandma
eats my grandma.
My grandma totally
eats your grandma.
Nuh-uh. If any grandma's doing
any eating, it's my grandma.
ELDRIDGE: No way.
JAKE: Come on.
My grandma has real teeth.
You happy?
ELDRIDGE:
How do you know?
JAKE:
She bit me once.
Well, that was great.
I'm really glad we got
to spend some time together.
Yeah, it was lovely.
Yeah. Oh, don't forget
we have that meeting
with the venture fund tomorrow.
Oh, yeah, right.
Bye.
Oh, bye.
Oh, do me a favor, Zoey.
Don't let him wear sandals
to the meeting.
I really don't tell him
what to wear.
That's okay. You'll learn.
Don't wear sandals
to the meeting.
Good night.
Night-night.
Bye. Drive safe.
Mm.
(sighs)
I think that went great.
Do you?
You don't?
I don't.
I don't, either.
Did... Um, did I miss something?
Obviously,
you missed everything.
That horrible woman
won't be happy
till she's destroyed
our relationship,
and she has you back.
What? No!
She has a boyfriend.
She's happy.
Oh, how can you be so smart
about some things
and so stupid about others?
Okay, wait, just to be clear,
what am I smart about
and what am I stupid about?!
Oh, what?
Now you can't hear me!
♪ Men. ♪
Anybody want more
mashed potatoes?
Oh, gosh, I'm
full, Jean,
but everything's
so delicious.
Thank you.
And how lucky were you to
grow up with Mom's home cooking?
Excuse me. You grew up
with home cooking, too.
Yes, but the maid
did the cooking.
It was still at home.
Make sure
you leave room for dessert.
I made pie.
Oh, I love Grandma's pie.
Yeah, yeah, I heard it, too.
(clinking spoon on glass)
There's something
I'd like to say.
Oh, dear God, here it comes.
It gives me such pleasure
to welcome Jean into my home
and to share our new friendship
with our two families.
Hear, hear.
And I'd just like to thank Evy
for showing me
that it's never too late to
teach an old dog new tricks.
Certainly didn't teach
her to fetch a bone.
Shh.
I have a question.
Oh, God, here it comes.
If you and her
were cannibals,
which do you think
would eat the other?
There you have it:
the upside of stupid.
ZOEY: I'm sorry, Walden,
but Bridget's right.
You have history with her;
you have none with me.
You can't even be sure
I love you for yourself
and not your money.
What are you saying?
I'm saying,
I think it might be better
for both of us
if we went our separate ways.
Okay, that's one approach...
which stinks.
So, let me make
a counterproposal.
Why don't you move in with me?
What?
Yeah, you and Ava
move in with me.
I love you,
and I want you in my life,
I want... I want
to have a future with you.
Really?
Really.
AVA: Mummy, Mummy,
please say yes!
What are you doing
out of bed?!
I love you, Walden!
I love you, Ava.
Get back into bed!
Hmm. Let's see.
So, that's one vote for yes,
and I vote yes,
so, the motion is passed.
There is one
tiny little problem.
What's that?
If Ava and I move in,
isn't somebody going
to have to move out?
Hmm.
(groans)
What's the matter?
I don't know.
Just felt a little shiver
go down my spine.
(groans)
♪ Men. ♪
Here you go.
I got to ask.
What's with the tea?
You make it for me.
You make it for Lyndsey.
Well, I've got
a little philosophy.
When someone's nice enough
to let me into their home
or their pants,
I like to show my appreciation.
Without spending
any money.
You know me so well.
So, recap.
How'd your dinner go?
Oh, pretty well, actually.
The grandmas were
on their best behavior,
and the two boys--
well, let's just say,
they're gonna be living with us
for a long, long time. And you?
Oh, good, good.
It went really good.
So, everything's okay with Zoey?
Yeah, it's fantastic.
Sounds like everything's great
with you and Lyndsey, huh?
Oh, yeah, more than good.
Oh, forgot the honey.
She owns her own home, right?
Yeah.
(groans)
Hmm. Think I may be coming down
with something.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net